Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 9=
(Wan, the way I treated you before)
(was because I didn't want
to drag you into this.)
Your wife is already dead.
Hand over the City Lord Token now,
and I might spare your life.
What's the point of living as a coward?
(I've had the same dream three times.)
(I've tried three times,)
(but still couldn't change our fate.)
(When I was young,
an elder once told me)
(about the prophecy
of "Four Dreams, One Life".)
(Never thought it'd all come true.)
(As he said,
this must be the final chance.)
(I wonder this time)
(if I can change the dream
and grow old with you.)
(Spirit Tablet of Deceased Mu Tianyou
Spirit Tablet of Deceased Chen Yueling)
Father.
Mother.
Today's your death anniversary.
I miss you both so much.
I have grown up.
Don't worry.
I'll never let you down.
I'll try my best
to protect Jin City's people
and safeguard Jin City.
It's been so many years.
Yunqing has grown up.
And he married Wan this year.
May your souls rest in peace now.
Father.
(Spirit Tablet of Deceased Mu Tianyou
Spirit Tablet of Deceased Chen Yueling)
Rest in peace.
Father, Mother.
Yunqing.
Your parents
were ambushed on their way back
from the capital
and both perished.
Your elder brother
was adopted years ago.
Now you must take on the responsibility
of being the City Lord.
(Spirit Tablet of Deceased Mu Tianyou
Spirit Tablet of Deceased Chen Yueling)
Yunqing.
Let the bygones be bygones.
Though this incident
started with Wan breaking the vase,
those who killed your parents
were from Mobei.
I know.
I've never blamed Wan.
Now Mobei grows more rampant.
They're our true enemy.
Glad that you understand this.
My teachings to you didn't go to waste.
Wan was adopted,
with a tragic background.
Don't let Wan
know about these matters.
Don't worry, Grandfather.
I'll take good care of Wan.
Good.
(Spirit Tablet of Deceased Mu Tianyou
Spirit Tablet of Deceased Chen Yueling)
(Shili Pavilion)
Never knew you could play the flute.
Mother forced me to learn it.
She said if my sister were alive,
she'd master all arts and music.
So I had to learn them too.
Later,
my sister vanished.
After that,
Mother put all her hopes
onto me.
But I...
It's all my fault.
Don't think that way.
Mother says Father died by Mobei hands.
And my sister vanished that same time.
So Mother forced me
to keep in mind the hatred
towards the Mobei people.
But I wasn't even born yet.
I can't fully understand her hatred.
I want to escape,
but can't leave Mother behind.
Don't think like that, Mr. Song.
Your mother loves you deeply.
Try talk it out with her?
You have no idea
that my mother has...
What?
Nothing.
She just wants me to be like her,
but I can't.
Don't open your eyes yet!
Wan, where are you taking me?
You'll know soon.
Are we there yet?
Not yet. Hold onto me. Don't worry.
Godmother, steps ahead.
One, two... There!
Are we there?
Almost there.
Let me help you sit down, Godmother.
Come over here. Sit down.
Why put on such a show?
Can I open my eyes now, Wan?
Yes, open your eyes.
W-What are these?
Godmother.
I heard Mr. Song mention
you had a daughter,
and she must be around my age now.
Godmother, my mother always said
a daughter is born and raised
by her mother's love.
Today, I wish to fulfill
that filial duty on her behalf.
Look!
This might be
her first attempt at painting.
Her very first portrait was of you.
In her mind,
her mother must be the one
she loved the most.
And this.
She bought this for you
after her adult ceremony.
And this.
She made this rouge
for your birthday.
She wished for your eternal youth,
free from burdens.
Wan, thank you. Thank you.
Godmother, if you don't mind,
could you tell me more about her?
Her name was Baozhu.
When she was a baby,
I took her to enjoy
the lantern festival,
and she was so excited.
Is this pretty?
Is it pretty?
Move!
My husband!
Hush now, don't cry.
Good girl.
(I was pregnant
with Qiming at the time,)
(so I had to leave Baozhu in the alley.)
(Who'd know that farewell
would be permanent?)
Baozhu's loss has been
the heaviest burden in my mind.
I searched for her,
but it was like finding
a needle in the ocean.
I found no trace.
My husband served as deputy general
to Mu Yunqing's father.
He was fatally poisoned,
beyond saving.
After giving birth to Qiming,
I never stopped
searching for my daughter.
Years had passed,
so I had no choice but
to leave with Qiming.
If I hadn't lost Baozhu,
I wouldn't be having
such a hard time now.
It's all my fault.
It was my fault.
Godmother.
She must stay alive.
You must believe that.
And now,
you have me.
I will take good care of you for Baozhu.
Let's move on.
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪